

# NUR FATIN KASSIRAN 930527-12-5530



### **EDUCATION**

O BACHELOR OF EDUCATION WITH HONOURS (EDUCATION WITH TESL)

at Universiti Malaysia Sabah, Kota Kinabalu.

**CGPA: 3.25** 

O SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA

at SMK Balung, Tawau. 2A, 2A-, 1B+, 3C, 1D



# **EXPERIENCES**

OMR DIY TRADING, BSW, TAWAU

July 11th 2017 – present (Cashier)

O SMK WAKUBA, TAWAU

March 2<sup>nd</sup> 2017 – 26<sup>th</sup> May 2017 (Replacement Teacher)

OSMK TAMAN TUN FUAD, KOTA KINABALU

Feb 28<sup>th</sup> 2016 – 15<sup>th</sup> July 2016 (Trainee Teacher)



#### **CO-CURRICULLAR**

#### O Universiti Malaysia Sabah (2012-2016)

- Exco of Publicity and Information (College)
- Committee Member of Family Day (College)
- Member of e-SeMTra (College)
- Participant of TESL Apprenticeship Programme 2015

#### O Labuan Matriculation College (2011-2012)

- Committee Member of Al-Irfan (Unit Kebersihan dan Keceriaan)
- Committee Member of Dinamika Dinner

#### OSMK Balung, Tawau (2009-2010)

Member of Police Cadet (School)



#### **PERSONALITY**













Teamwork Organized

Flexible

Motivated

Creative

Multitask



#### REFERENCE

O Mohd Jamalulail bin Ismail **Assistant Branch Manager** MR DIY (EM) SDN BHD Tawau

016-388 0453

O Abdul Latif bin Antong Senior Assistant SMK Wakuba XEA3072, p/s 61835, 91028 Tawau, Sabah.

019-863 9406

#### BIOGRAPHY

Fatin, 24 years old, single. Can be described as a dedicated person, strong-willed, easily adapt cooperative.



#### **CONTACTS**

- Batu 22, Jalan Apas Balung, Peti Surat 62274, 91032 Tawau, Sabah.
- 0115-167 1869 / 019-863 5847
- fatinkassiran275@gmail.com



#### **SKILLS**

MS Words **MS Power Point** MS Excel SPSS v21 Sony Vegas Movie Maker

Driving (DA)



## LANGUAGES

English (Spoken) English (Written) Malay (Spoken) Malay (Written)





# **INTERESTS**











